Real estate is a very diversified
and cluttered market. It's not easy for a retail investor to
start investing in this. To simplify this process,
we are trying to build beautiful, simple,
and easy-to-use products. We believe everything starts with
exploring what's latest in the real estate market.
Easy Acre is a simple website to explore global news and a chat
tool specified to you for your,
real estate needs. Let's explore a premium market.
I'm selecting Bangalore, India here.
Here we will be having all the quarterly report,
the rental yields, price per square foot,
average price and other premium markets of the country of India.
We can select any other
city as well. Like, I'm selecting Abu Dhabi.
So, here we will be having.
All the latest one, we can change or select any other market
to explore more about Abu Dhabi. This is an inside of the news,
we can click on the news, it will redirect to the actual news,
article where we can read the full article.
If you want to know more about that, article.
We can click on the Easy Acre,
chat tool. This will help you understand what,
this will summarize and help you discuss about this particular
news, what's, what is in this article and if you have any questions,
we can discuss that. that with the AI chat tool.
along with that, you can always select general.
If you doesn't want to know about the Abu Dhabi specifically general news about
real estate or general queries about real estate,
we can always. Chat as a general,
and let's see how to apply for home
loan. It will give you insight based on what
are the latest. documents required or what are the credit scores
to be matched for the home loans and you can continue discussing on
that. We can access the chat.
On the top right as well,
like ask easy acre. This will also open the chat bot,
the real estate chat bot, which you can use.
Yeah, that's all. Thank you.